Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Dairy Queen Blizzard flavors,
but lower in calories and higher in
protein. This is the Royal Reese's
Fluffern Nuttered Blizzard. Let me show
you how to make it. Starting off with a
classic vanilla base. This is what Dairy
Queen uses, so we are going to copy
that. The recipe for this will be down
in the description. We're going to blend
all those ingredients up. Throw it in
the freezer for at least 16 hours. Let
run under hot water for about a minute.
And throw it in our creamy on the light
ice cream setting. While that is
running, we can get our mixins. To best
recreate this, we're going to need a
peanut butter swirl. So, to make that,
we're going to combine some peanut
butter chips with a little bit of
coconut oil. Throw that in the microwave
for about 30 seconds, and then mix until
it's nice and smooth. That light ice
cream cycle should be about done now.
So, we're going to take it out, scrape
down the sides of your ice cream, all
out a hole in the middle, and throw in
your chopped peanut butter cups along
with that peanut butter mixture. And
then throw all that back in on the
mixing setting. Now, you could just eat
it like this. It is phenomenal. But to
get that true royal factor of a Dairy
Queen Blizzard, we need to stuff this
thing. So, we're going in with this
thick white marshmallow cream.